( Radio static )
( Static continues )
( Static cuts out )
( Wind rustles gently )
( Soft ethereal music )
( Music builds )
( Gulls cawing )
( Waves lapping )
( Music stops )
( Gulls caw )
( Waves lapping )
( Gull caws )
( Gull cawing )
( Water drips )
( Rock clatters )
( Soft ethereal music )
( Birdsong )
( Music stops )
( Ticking )
( Motor starts up )
( Whirring )
( Whirring continues )
( ♪ " The Bristol Christ " plays on radio )
♪ Swim on
♪ Captain Jesus
♪ Wherever you may wish
♪ Right on
♪ The wicked water
♪ The message of the fish
♪ Heal in the holy river
- ♪ River - ♪ River
♪ Your five fingered scars
♪ Turn like a tree about the sea
♪ Your skeleton of spars ♪
( Whirring )
( Static )
( Static continues ) ( Ticking )
( Radio beeps )
( Man ) ' Come in . '
Can you hear me ?
Just to let you know , should be with you by the end of the week .
Weather permitting .
- Over and out . ' - ( Radio beeps )
( Whirring )
( Whirring peters out )
( Footsteps receding )
( Faint horn )
( Wind rustles gently )
( Soft ethereal music )
( Music stops )
( Waves lapping )
( Gulls cawing )
( Water drips )
( Rock clatters )
( Footsteps approaching )
( Soft ethereal music )
( Music builds )
( Music continues )
( Music stops )
( Motor starts up )
( Whirring )
( Ticking ) ( Feet scraping )
( Man on radio ) ' ... described the immense distress felt
at finding the statue surrounded by smashed glass
and daubed with offensive slogans .
The memorial , a carved granite figure , which stands looking out over the bay ,
was unveiled in front of a large crowd nearly 50 years ago
and is an important local landmark standing on watch ,
casting an eye over the comings and goings on the water .
The statue was erected in memory of a popular local boatman
who was lost on the 1st of May 1973 ,
near the old Miners ' Quay on the abandoned island of Enys Men .
The monument has become a focal point for the collective grief of so many
who have experienced the loss of a friend or family member at sea . '
( Whirring )
' It is apparent there is much shock , sadness and anger
following the vandalisation of the figure over the weekend . '
( Generator whirring )
( Radio whistles then beeps )
( Woman over radio ) ' Are you lonely ? '
( Static ) ( Beep )
( Woman 2 ) ' Not really . '
( Beep ) ( Static )
( Woman ) ' How 's the work ? '
( Static ) ( Beep )
( Woman 2 ) ' Fine . '
It 's why I 'm here .
( Static ) ( Beep )
Supply boat 'll be here soon .
( Static )
( Woman ) ' Are you running short ? '
( Static ) ( Beep )
Petrol 's low .
And I 'm nearly out of tea .
( Beep ) ( Static )
( Static continues )
( Handle clicks )
( Soft creaking )
( Soft creaking ) ( Door closes )
( Soft ethereal music )
( Music fades out )
( Music stops )
( Rhythmic tapping )
( Tapping continues )
( Waves lapping )
( Water drips )
( Rock clatters )
( Gentle clang )
( Soft rumbling )
( Soft ethereal music )
( Birdsong )
( Gulls cawing )
( Caws ) ( Music fades out )
( Caws )
( Caws ) ( Waves lapping )
( Cawing )
( Waves lapping )
( Waves lapping loudly )
( Door creaking )
( Ticking )
Please don 't climb up there .
I don 't wanna keep telling you , but I have to .
I have to .
( Wind rustles gently )
( Ethereal vocalising )
( Soft ethereal music builds )
( Music fades out )
( Wind rustles gently ) ( Gate creaks open )
( Switch clicks )
( Motor starts up )
( Piano music plays over radio )
( Music continues )
( Kettle whistling )
( Piano music fades out )
( Waves lapping )
( Gasping )
( Water drips )
( Rock clatters )
( Soft ethereal music )
( Music builds )
( Music continues )
( Ticking )
( Music fades out )
( Girl ) " Oven " .
( Music starts up again )
( Switch clicks )
( Motor starts up )
( Generator whirring ) ( Music fades out )
( Generator whirring faintly )
( Soft clanging )
( Whirring stops )
( Ticking )
( Silence )
( Motor starts up )
( Whirring )
( Generator whirring )
( Beep ) ( Static )
( Static continues from radio )
( Kettle humming )
( Woman over radio ) ' You there ? '
( Radio beeps )
' Hello ? "
- ( Beep ) - ' Hello ? '
( Soft ethereal music )
( Music continues )
( Music fades out )
( Generator whirrs , then peters out )
( Clattering )
( Wind rustles gently )
( Silence )
( Waves lapping )
( Tense sound )
( Soft ethereal music )
( Gulls cawing )
( Music fades )
( Water drips )
( Rock clatters )
( Eerie rumbling resonates ) ( Water drips )
( Water drips )
( Dripping continues )
( Dripping continues ) ( Eerie rumbling )
( Rock clatters )
( Soft ethereal music )
( Birdsong )
( Music continues )
( Birdsong continues )
( Music fades out ) ( Radio static )
( Static continues )
( High-pitched frequency builds over radio )
( Sound of baby crying )
( Frequency becomes louder ) ( Crying continues )
( Silence )
( Soft ethereal music )
( Waves lapping )
( Music builds )
( Music fades out )
( Eerie rumbling resonates )
( Silence )
( Bell tolls )
( Soft ethereal music )
( Music continues )
( High-pitched melody )
( Music fades out )
( Wind rustles gently )
( ♪ Children singing " Kan Me " by Gwenno )
( Singing continues )
( Door opens )
( Singing gets louder )
( Door closes ) ( Singing gets quieter )
( Singing continues )
( Singing stops )
Who 's there ?
( Silence )
( Pulsating high-frequency )
( Eerie singing )
( Soft ethereal music ) ( Eerie singing )
( Eerie singing continues ) ( Music continues )
- ( Beep ) - ( Man over radio ) ' Approaching . '
( Radio static )
- ' Approaching . ' - ( Beep )
' Approaching . '
( Soft ethereal music )
( Waves lapping )
( Music fades out )
( Ticking )
( Generator whirring )
( Soft ethereal music )
( Whirring continues )
( Music fades out )
( Door opens )
( Wind rustles gently )
( Generator whirring )
( Blades whirring )
- ( Beep ) - ( Man over radio ) ' I 'm standing by . Over . '
( Blades whirring ) ( Silence )
( ♪ GWENNO : " Kan Me " plays over radio )
( Turns radio off )
( Wind rustles gently )
( Ticking )
( Lock clicks )
( Door opens )
( Door clicks )
( Zips jacket )
( Soft ethereal music )
( Waves lapping )
( Dramatic note resonates )
( Note builds )
( Note fades )
( Door opens )
( Ticking )
( Wind rustles gently )
( Water dripping )
( Dripping continues ) ( Generator whirring )
( Whirring continues )
( Radio beeps ) ( Static )
( Woman over radio ) ' Are you there ? '
( Static continues )
- ' Hello ? ' - ( Beep )
- ' Can you hear me ? ' - ( Beep )
( Soft ethereal music builds )
- ( Beep ) - ' Can you hear me ? '
( Radio beeps )
- ' Are you ... " - ( Sound cuts out )
( Water dripping )
( Motor fails )
( Horn sounds )
( Rumbling resonates )
( Creaking )
( Silence )
( Dripping )
( Dripping continues )
( Dramatic note )
( Ethereal vocalising )
( Dripping )
( Dripping continues )
( Bell tolls )
( Soft ethereal music )
( Water drips )
( Rock clatters )
( Tense note builds )
( Man coughing )
( Soft ethereal music )
( Music continues )
Trim your feeble lamp , my sister .
( Water dripping )
( Dripping )
( Dripping continues )
( Rumbling resonates )
( Dripping gets louder )
( Dripping continues )
( Dripping stops )
( Tense resonating )
( Wind rustles gently )
( Gulls cawing )
( Birdsong )
( Man coughing )
( Coughing continues )
( Step creaks )
( Man coughing )
( Coughing continues )
( Toilet flushes )
( Door creaking )
( Footsteps approaching )
( Footsteps receding )
( Lock clicks )
( Soft ethereal music )
( Waves lapping )
( Music continues )
( Children giggling )
( Giggling continues )
( Gull caws )
( Bird song )
( Lock clicks )
( Ticking )
( Dramatic note resonates )
( Fades out )
( Footsteps approach )
( Children giggling )
( Giggling continues )
( Footsteps recede ) ( Giggling stops )
( Faint rhythmic tapping )
( ♪ Children singing " Kan Me " )
♪ Rag dynerghi an howlwyn
♪ Diweth an gwav gweinton brav
♪ Daleth an hav
♪ Ottoma an spern gwyn
♪ Rag dynerghi an howlwyn
♪ Diweth an gwav gweinton brav
♪ Daleth an hav
♪ Daleth an hav ( Rag dynerghi an howlwyn )
♪ Diweth an gwav gweinton brav ( Diweth an gwav gweinton brav )
♪ Kan me kana
♪ Kan me kana ( Daleth an hav )
♪ Daleth an hav
Who 's there ?
( Birdsong )
( Pop music plays over radio )
( Music continues loudly over radio )
( Music quietens )
( Water trickles )
( Music continues )
- ( Beep ) - ( Man over radio ) ' Approaching . '
- ( Music stops ) - ( Static )
- ( Beep ) - Hello ?
- ( Beep ) - ' Approaching . '
Hello ?
( Static )
( Pop music plays again )
( Waves lapping )
( Silence )
( Soft ethereal music )
( Music builds )
( Radio chatter )
( Chatter continues )
( Man over radio ) ' Mayday . Mayday . Mayday .
This is supply boat Govenek .
Mayday ! This is supply boat Govenek . '
( Tense resonation drowns out radio message )
( Soft ethereal music )
Dark the night of sin has settled .
( Music builds )
( Rumbling resonates )
( Silence )
( Dramatic note resonates )
( Lock clicks )
( Horn sounds )
Couldn 't reach you on the radio !
I got no power !
( Petrol sloshes )
( Motor fails )
( Whirring )
- ( Whirring continues ) - ( over TV ) ... Torpoint Athletic nil .
Holsworthy 0-0 St Blazey .
Nanpean Rovers 2-1 Newquay .
Newport 1-1 Watling Town .
Truro City 0-2 Porthleven .
Liskeard Athletic 0-0 Saltash United .
Falmouth Town 1-1 Penzance . '
( Report becomes indistinct )
Thought you weren 't supposed to pick ' em ?
( Whirring continues )
I didn 't .
( Report continues over TV )
( Whirring continues )
Do you like it here on your own ?
I 'm not on my own .
( Soft dramatic music )
( Wind howls )
( Sound cuts out )
( Ticking )
- ( Beep ) - ( Man ) ' Mayday . Mayday . Mayday .
This is Govenek . Govenek . Govenek . '
( Static )
' Mayday . Mayday . Mayday .
This is Govenek . Govenek . Govenek . '
( Static )
' Mayday . Mayday . Mayday .
This is Govenek . Govenek . Govenek .
Mayday . Mayday . Mayday .
This is Govenek . '
( Dramatic note resonates )
( Faint whirring of generator )
( Report continues over TV )
( Boatman ) Best be off .
( Water drips )
You should stay .
You know I can 't .
No .
Call me .
( Radio beeps )
( Man ) ' Mayday . Mayday . This is Govenek .
- Govenek . Govenek . ' - ( Loud whirring )
' Mayday . Mayday . Mayday .
This is Govenek . Govenek . Govenek . '
( Screaming )
( Tense notes )
( Dramatic music )
( Horn sounds )
( Gull caws )
( Waves lapping )
( Man singing )
( Man ) ♪ Let the lower lights be burning
♪ Send a gleam across the wave
♪ Some poor fainting , struggling seaman
♪ You may rescue , you may save
♪ Dark the night of sin has settled
♪ Loud the angry billows roar
♪ Eager eyes are watching , longing
♪ For the lights along the shore
♪ Let the lower lights be burning
♪ Send a gleam across the wave
♪ Some poor fainting , struggling seaman
♪ You may rescue
♪ You may save
♪ Trim your feeble lamp , my sister
♪ Some poor sailor tempest-tossed
♪ Trying now to make the harbour
♪ In the darkness may be lost
♪ Let the lower lights be burning
♪ Send a gleam across the wave
♪ Some poor fainting , struggling seaman
♪ You may rescue
♪ You may save ♪
( Waves lapping )
( Bell tolls )
( Rumbling resonates )
( Footsteps approaching )
( Whirring )
( Resonating continues )
( Soft ethereal music )
( Music builds )
( Beep )
( Rumble resonates )
( Beeping )
( Beep )
Fuck !
( Beeping )
( Beep )
( Silence )
( Tense note builds )
( Blades whirring )
( Static )
( Man ) ' Mayday . Mayday . Mayday . '
- This is Govenek . Govenek . Govenek . ' - ( Beep )
' Mayday . Mayday . Mayday .
This is Govenek . Govenek . Govenek . '
( Static )
( Static continues )
( Faint electronic music )
( Radio beeps )
( Sailor over radio ) ' We 're just off Carn Dhu ,
and heading to Harbour Cove , where the old Miners ' Quay used to be ,
- see what we can find . Over . ' - ( Beep )
- ( Beep ) - ( Pilot ) ' I 'm standing by . Over . '
( Beep )
( Silence )
( Sound cuts back in )
( Loud whirring )
( Sound distorts )
( Ticking )
( Radio beeps )
( Static )
Hello ?
Is there anybody there ?
( Man coughing )
Can you hear me ?
( Beep )
( Woman ) Hello ?
- Is there anybody there ? - ( Beep )
Can you hear me ?
( Beep )
( Sailor ) ' We 're just off Carn Dhu ...
and heading to Harbour Cove , where the old Miners ' Quay used to be ,
- see what we can find . Over . ' - ( Beep )
- ( Beep ) - ( Woman panting )
( Woman ) Is there anybody there ?
( Panting )
- ( Beep ) - ( Pilot ) ' I 'm standing by . Over . '
( Woman ) Can you hear me ?
( Rumbling resonates )
( Water drips )
( Rock clatters )
- ( Rock clatters ) - ( Man coughing )
( Coughing continues )
( Rock clatters )
( Rumbling resonates )
( Gravel crunching )
( Water dripping )
( Radio static ) ( Distorted music )
( Static continues ) ( Music continues )
( Distorted speech over radio )
( High-pitched static )
( Static stops ) ( Music continues )
( Thud )
( Soft ethereal music )
( Distorted static )
( Distorted static continues ) ( Stomping feet continue )
( Music builds )
( Sound cuts out ) ( Music softens )
( High-pitched note wavers )
( Silence )
( Waves lapping )
( Birdsong )
( Water drips )
( Rock clatters )
( Soft ethereal music )
( Music continues )
( Music fades )
( Wind rustles gently )
( Sound cuts out )
( Radio static builds )
( Rhythmic tapping )
♪ Ottoma an spern gwyn
♪ Rag dynerghi an howlwyn
♪ Diweth an gwav gweinton brav
♪ Daleth an hav
♪ Kan me kana
♪ Daleth an hav .
( ♪ GWENNO : " Kan Me " )
♪ Ottoma an spern gwyn
♪ Rag dynerghi an howlwyn
♪ Diweth an gwav gweinton brav
♪ Daleth an hav
♪ Ottoma an spern gwyn
♪ Rag dynerghi an howlwyn
♪ Diweth an gwav gweinton brav
♪ Daleth an hav
♪ Kan me kana
( Song continues )
♪ Daleth an hav ( Rag dynerghi an howlwyn )
♪ Kan me kana
♪ Daleth an hav .